Guide to the Velvet Underground Collection, 1964-2015.
Velvet Underground Collection,
- Publications, 1964-2007
  - Newspapers, magazines, and other publications, 1966-2009
    - Creem, November 1987 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      Lou Reed and the Velvet Underground - The Final Truth
    - Dazed and Confused, September 2009 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      Vol. 2 Issue 77
      Unseen Archives: Velvet Underground
    - Different Times, 1979 -1983 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      2, 2.5, 3, 4, 6
    - Different Times, June 1980 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      "The Velvet Underground and After… Fifteen Years of Shock Waves From The Exploding Plastic Inevitable - A 'Diferent Times' Special"
    - The East Village Other, March 1, 1967-March 15, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      Vol. 2, No. 7
    - The East Village Other, May 1, 1967-May 15, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      Vol. 2, No. 11
    - The East Village Other, May 12, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      Vol. 5, No. 24
    - Electric Frog, June 1967 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Evergreen Review, June 1967 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Issue 47
    - Forced Exposure, June 1985-September 1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Friez, June 1993-September 1993 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Issue 11
    - Fusion, April 14, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      No. 8
    - Fusion, September 5, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      No. 16
    - Fusion, March 6, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 3-4)
      No. 28
    - Fusion, September 18, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 5-6)
      No. 40
    - Fusion, February 5, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      No. 49
    - Fusion, April 1969 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - GO, June 13, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      No. 169
    - Hit Parader, June 1975 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Hullabaloo, June 1968 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - In-Beat, November 1966 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - It, February, 25 1971 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      Issue 97
    - Jazz and Pop, February 1968 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Vol. 7, No. 2
    - Jazz and Pop, June 1969 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      Vol. 8, No. 6
    - Kicks, March 1979-June 1979 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      Issue 1
    - KYA Beat, December 31, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Les Inrockuptibles, July 1990-August 1990 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      Issue 24
      The Velvet Underground and Andy Warhol
    - Les Inrockuptibles, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      Superstars* *Guide maniaque du Velvet Underground et de la Factory d'Andy Warhol
    - Les Inrockuptibles, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      The Velvet Underground - Special Issue
    - Lid, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      Issue 2
      3 copies
    - LIFE Magazine, May 27, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - LIFE Magazine, February 17, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Little Caesar, January 1971-March 1971 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      Issue 7
    - Los Angeles Free Press, October 25, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 15-16)
      Vol. 5, No. 43 (Part 1 and 2)
    - Lula: Girl of my Dreams, March 2007-September 2007 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Issue 4
    - Lula: Girl of my Dreams, March 2008-September 2008 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Issue 6
    - Mojo, May 2005 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Issue 138
      "People Are Really Stupid…" Lou Reed: A Lifetime of Pains with Rock's Mr. Angry. 2 copies.
    - Mojo, December 2009; CD-3241 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      Issue 193
      Includes CD "Mojo Presents The Wall Rebuilt! Disc One."
    - Musician, April 1989 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      Issue 126
      The Velvet Overview: Lou Reed and John Cale - A Historic Reunion
    - New York Times, October 15, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      Single page with an ad for the Exploding Plastic Inevitible Returns at the Ballroom Farm 23 St. Marks Place
    - New Times, April 20, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - NME: New Musical Express, April 25, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      Velvet Underground: The Definitive History of the Greatest Cult Band of All
    - NY Rocker, July 1980-August 1980 (Box 12, Folder 19-20)
      "The Velvet Underground (1965-1990) an inevitable explosion." Two copies.
    - Open City, November 15, 1968-November 21, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      Issue 178
      "Velvet Underground Raps" article.
    - Other Scenes, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 21)
      Vol. 3, No. 13
    - Pageant, March 1967 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      Vol. 22 Issue 9
    - Penetration, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      Steve Took, Henry Cow, Beefheart, Kevin Ayers, The Velvet Underground, and much more
    - Poppin, May 1969 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      Vol. 1, No. 2
      "Lee Michaels, John Mayall, Velvet Underground, and more" 2 copies.
    - Realities, August 1967 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      No. 259
    - Record Collector, September 2001 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      Issue 265
      Velvet Underground: Moe Tucker and Doug Yule interviewed
    - Record Collector, May 2005 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      Issue 310
      Velvet Underground: The Ultimate Rarity
    - Record Collector's Magazine, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      Vol. 21, No. 9
      The Velvet Underground and Nico, 41 page feature in Japanese
    - Record World, October 19, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      Vol. 23, No. 1115
    - Rock Magazine Comics, August 10, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      Issue 5
      Descnendant of the Sisyphus Starring: John Cale [sic]
    - SoundMakers, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Temporary Thing, August 15, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Temporary Thing, February 15, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      Issue 8
      With copies of cover of #5 and #7
    - Thirdear, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - TimeOut, October 8, 1971-October 14, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      Velvet Underground: The Janitors of Lunacy - on the college circuit
    - UCLA Daily Bruin, January 20, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 23)
      "Orbiting the Periphery of Pop: The Velvet Underground and friends"
    - Ugly Things, March 2009-June 2009 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Issue 28
    - Uncut, December 2009 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      The Velvet Underground
    - Varulven, September 1977 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - The Velvet Underground, June 1995-December 1995 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      Vol. 4
      Edited by The Swiss Army for Fierce Pup Productions
    - The Velvet Underground, January 1996-June 1996 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      Vol. 5
    - Vibrations, July 1967 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Vibrations, September 1968 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      Issue 10
    - Vibrations, November 1970-December 1970 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      No. 25
    - The Village Voice, February 10, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      Vol. XI, No. 17
    - The Village Voice, March 31, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Vol. XI, No. 24
    - The Village Voice, April 7, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      Vol. XI, No. 25
    - The Village Voice, April 14, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Vol. XI, No. 26
    - The Village Voice, April 28, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Vol. XI, No. 28
    - The Village Voice, September 29, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      Vol. XI, No. 50
    - The Village Voice, October 6, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Vol. XI, No. 51
    - The Village Voice, October 13, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      Vol. XI, No. 52
    - The Village Voice, October 20, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 9-10)
      Vol. XII, No. 1
      Two Copies
    - The Village Voice, January 5, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      Vol. XII, No. 12
    - The Village Voice, February 2, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      Vol. XII, No. 16
    - The Village Voice, February 9, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      Vol. XII, No. 17
    - The Village Voice, February 16, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 14-15)
      Vol. XII, No. 18
    - The Village Voice, March 30, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      Vol. XII, No. 24
    - The Village Voice, April 6, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      Vol. XII, No. 25
    - The Village Voice, April 13, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 18-19)
      Vol. XII, No. 26
    - The Village Voice, April 20, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      Vol. XII, No. 27
    - The Village Voice, April 27, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      Vol. XII, No. 28
    - VIP: The Playboy Club Magazine, September 1966-December 1966 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      No. 11
    - What Goes On: The Official Magazine of the Velvet Underground Appreciation Society, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      No. 1
      2 copies.
    - What Goes On: The Official Magazine of the Velvet Underground Appreciation Society, June 1979 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      No. 2
    - What Goes On: The Official Magazine of the Velvet Underground Appreciation Society, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      No. 3
    - What Goes On: The Official Magazine of the Velvet Underground Appreciation Society, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      The best of 1 and 2
    - What Goes On: The Official Magazine of the Velvet Underground Appreciation Society, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      No. 4
    - What Goes On: The Official Magazine of the Velvet Underground Appreciation Society, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      No. 5
    - Wire, April 2001; CD-3242 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      No. 206
      Early Minimalism: Tom Ze, Keith Rowe, Matmos, John Cale - Inside the Dream Syndicate
    - World Countdown: Music Newspaper, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 24)
      Vol. 2, No. 5
    - Zigzag, October 1970 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Zigzag, March 1971 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      No. 18
    - Zigzag, May 1971 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      No. 20
  - Poetry, 1964-1976
    - "Way Out: A Poem in Discord" by Gregory Corso, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Starstreams Poetry Series Number 1. Bardo Matrix, Kathmandu, Nepal 1974.
    - "7 Marvels" by Ira Cohen, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Starstreams Poetry Series Number 2. Bardo Matrix, Kathmandu, Nepal 1975.
    - "7 Poems" By Charles Henri Ford, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      Starstreams Poetry Series Number 3. Bardo Matrix, Kathmandu, Nepal, 1974
    - "The Subliminal Report" by Angus Maclise, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Starstreams Poetry Series Number 4. Bardo Matrix, Kathmandu, Nepal, 1975.
    - "Next to Normal" by Paul Bowles, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Starstreams Poetry Series Number 5. Bardo Matrix, Kathmandu, Nepal, 1976.
    - "Ckrowww" by Jane Falk, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Starstreams Poetry Series Number 6. Bardo Matrix, Kathmandu, Nepal, 1977.
    - "Opium Elementals" - Images by Dana Young, Poems by Ira Cohen, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      A Starstreams Poetry Special Edition. Bardo Matrix, Kathmandu, Nepal 1976.
    - "Exits" by Iris M. Gaynor, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      A Starstreams Poetry Special Edition. Bardo Matrix, Kathmandu, Nepal 1977.
    - "Gilded Splinters - Poems by Ira Cohen", 1977 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - "Poem for La Malinche" by Ira Cohen, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Bardo Matrix, Kathmandu, Nepal, 1974
    - "The Clearing Stage" by Roberto Francisco Valenza, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      Bardo Matrix, Kathmandu, Nepal, 1976
    - "Universal Mutant" by Ira Cohen, Undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - "Universal Mutant", Undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
      Single page, poem and illustration. Different poem from previous. Does not appear to be Bardo Matrix.
    - Perstare, March 1964-June 1964 (Box 21)
      Small press poetry anthology published by New York University
  - Velvet Underground, 1973-2007
    - c/o The Velvet Underground New York, N.Y., 2007 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Feed-back: The Legend of the Velvet Underground, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      By Ignacio Julia. The official, authorized english translation by Orly Fainstein and Margaret Kopp
    - Los Primitivos - Feed-back, Ruta 66, 1987; SR-10336 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      33 1/3 RPM, 7”. Demo recording.
    - Lou Reed and the Velvet Underground, Undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
      Bound Booklet
    - Lou Reed and the Velvets, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      By Nigel Trevana
    - The Rock Marketplace - Book of Rock n Roll Ads, Undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - The Velvet Underground, Undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
      By Carlo Albertoli
- Recordings, 1965-2012
  - Records, 1965-2012
    - 10 and 12 inch discs, 1965-2012
      - Lou Reed. Various artists. Soundsville! Teen Sounds. [N.p.]: Design Records, [1965], ©1962. Cat. no. DLP-187., 1965; SR-9717 (Box 22)
        Featuring Lou Reed (uncredited) on three songs: The Roughnecks’ “You’re Driving Me Insane” and the Beachnuts’ “I’ve Got a Tiger In My Tank” and “Cycle Annie.” Black label.
      - Lou Reed. The Surfsiders. The Surfsiders Sing the Beach Boys Songbook. [N.p.]: Design Records, [1965]., 1965; SR-9718 (Box 22)
        Featuring performances by an uncredited Lou Reed. Cat. no. SDLP-208.
      - Lou Reed. Ronnie Dove & Terry Phillips. Swingin’ Teen Sounds of Ronnie Dove & Terry Phillips. [N.p.]: Design Records, [1965]. Cat. no. DLP-186. 3 songs are co-written by Lou Reed:”This Rose,” “Flowers for the Lady,” and “Wild One.” Canadian pressing, with red label., 1965; SR-9719 (Box 22)
      - The Velvet Underground. The Velvet Underground and Nico. Verve Records, V-5008., 1967; SR-9720 (Box 22)
        First issue, mono, with unaltered back cover. Sealed, with cover sticker intact.
      - The Velvet Underground. The Velvet Underground and Nico. Verve Records, V6-5008., 1967; SR-9721 (Box 22)
        Second issue, stereo, with airbrushed back cover. Sealed, with cover sticker intact.
      - The Velvet Underground. The Velvet Underground and Nico. Verve Records, SVLP 9184., 1967; SR-9722 (Box 22)
        UK pressing, with airbrushed back cover image from the American version used as the front cover instead of the Warhol banana.
      - The Velvet Underground. The Velvet Underground and Nico. Verve Records. V-5008., 1967 (Box 22)
        Sleeve only from the altered first issue, with sticker over top quarter of back cover. Banana picker approximately 40% peeled.
      - The Velvet Underground. White Light/White Heat. MGM/Verve, V/V6-5046., 1968; SR-9723 (Box 22)
        Stereo. Sealed.
      - The Velvet Underground. White Light/White Heat. MGM/Verve, V/V6-5046., 1968; SR-9724 (Box 22)
        Stereo.
      - The Velvet Underground. White Light/White Heat. MGM/Verve, V-5046., 1968; SR-9725 (Box 22)
        Promotional copy, labeled “Disc Jockey Record, Not For Sale.”
      - Tom Wilson. The Music Factory: Tom Wilson and Guests – The Velvet Underground. [N.p.]: MGM Records, 1968; SR-9726 (Box 22)
        Cat. no. MFRS-3. 2-LP promotional recording of a prerecorded radio program, featuring an interview with the Velvet Underground by host Tom Wilson. With accompanying mimeographed cue sheet (2 p.).
      - Tom Wilson. The Music Factory: Tom Wilson and Guests – The Velvet Underground. [N.p.]: MGM Records, 1968; SR-9726a (Box 22)
      - The Velvet Underground. The Velvet Underground. MGM Records, SE-4617., 1969; SR-9727 (Box 22)
      - The Velvet Underground. The Velvet Underground. MGM Records, SE-4617., 1969; SR-9728 (Box 22)
        Stereo. A second copy.
      - The Velvet Underground. The Velvet Underground. MGM Records, SE-4617., 1969; SR-9729 (Box 22)
        Stereo. Containing Lou Reed’s “Closet Mix” of the album.
      - The Velvet Underground. Loaded. Cotillion Records, SD 9034., 1970; SR-9730 (Box 22)
        Sterling Morrison’s copy, with accompanying statement of provenance signed by Jeffrey Gold/ Recordmecca.
      - The Velvet Underground. Loaded. Cotillion Records, SD 9034., 1970; SR-9731 (Box 22)
        Sealed.
      - The Velvet Underground. Loaded. Atlantic Records, 2400111., 1971; SR-9732 (Box 22)
      - Nico. Chelsea Girl. [UK]: MGM Records, Cat. no. 2353025., 1971; SR-9733 (Box 22)
      - The Velvet Underground. The Velvet Underground Live at Max’s Kansas City. Cotillion Records, SD 9500., 1972; SR-9734 (Box 22)
      - The Velvet Underground. (And so on.) Australia: Plastic Inevitable Records., 1982; SR-9735 (Box 22)
        Bootleg LP. Cat. no. SECOND-1.
      - The Velvet Underground. The Black Side of the Street. Australia: Incredible Recordmakers., 1983; SR-9736 (Box 22)
        Bootleg LP.
      - The Velvet Underground. Orange Disaster. [N.p.]: Clean Sound Records., 1984; SR-9737 (Box 22)
        Bootleg LP. Cat. no. CS 1005.
      - The Velvet Underground. Evil Mothers: Rare Velvets. [N.p.]: Skydog, Cat. no. Skydog LP 003., 1984; SR-9738 (Box 22)
        Reissue of a bootleg originally released in 1974.
      - The Velvet Underground. Legend. [N.p.: No label.], 1986; SR-9739 (Box 22)
        Bootleg LP with textless, floral label in generic white sleeve with ms. tracklist. Matrix number T-001.
      - The Velvet Underground and Nico. Down For You Is Up. [N.p.]: Easy Flyte Records., 1986; SR-9740 (Box 22)
        Bootleg LP. Cat. no. Flight 101. Recorded live in Cleveland, Nov. 4, 1966.
      - The Velvet Underground. Praise Ye the Lord. [N.p.: No label], 1988; SR-9741 (Box 22)
        Bootleg LP. Cat. no. VU 714.
      - The Velvet Underground. Something Different. [N.p.: No label], 2001; SR-9742 (Box 22)
        Bootleg LP. Cat. no. VU 6567
      - The Velvet Underground. Prominent Men. Bruxelles, Belgium: Arkain Filloux, 2012; SR-9743 (Box 22)
    - 7 inch discs, 1965-2011
      - Lou Reed. The All Night Workers. “Don’t Put All Your Eggs in One Basket” b/w “Why Don’t You Smile.” Round Sound, Cat. no. RS-1., 1965; SR-9744 (Box 24)
        “Why Don’t You Smile” co-written by Reed.
      - Lou Reed. The Intimates. “I’ve Got a Tiger In My Tank” b/w “Smart Too Late.” Epic Records, Cat. no. 5-9743., 1965; SR-9745 (Box 24)
        Side A co-written by Reed. Promotional copy.
      - The Velvet Underground. “All Tomorrow's Parties/I'll Be Your Mirror.” Verve Records, Cat. no. VK-10427., July 1966; SR-9746 (Box 24)
        Promotional 7” single in picture sleeve. Labeled "Special Disc Jockey Record.”
      - The Velvet Underground and Nico. “Femme Fatale” b/w “Sunday Morning. Verve, Cat. no. VK-10466., 1966; SR-9747 (Box 24)
        “Special Disc Jockey Record.”
      - The Riats. “Run Run Run” b/w “Sunday Morning.” [Netherlands]: Omega, Cat. no. 35.796., 1967; SR-9748 (Box 24)
        The first recorded cover versions of Velvet Underground songs.
      - The Velvet Underground. “White Light/White Heat” and “Here She Comes Now.” New York: Unidentified manufacturer, for Verve Records., September 28, 1967; SR-9749- SR-9750 (Box 24)
        Two 7” test pressings of the Verve single. “Given to Robert Quine by Lou Reed, sold to Michael Carlucci, who sold it to Scott Curran”—ms. note in the hand of Johan Kugelberg.
      - The Velvet Underground. “White Light/White Heat” b/w “Here She Comes Now.” Verve, Cat. no. VK-10560., 1967; SR-9751 (Box 24)
      - The Velvet Underground. “What Goes On” b/w “Jesus.” MGM, Cat. no. K-14057., 1969; SR-9752 (Box 24)
      - The Velvet Underground. The Velvet Underground. MGM Records, Cat. no. VU-1., 1969; SR-9753 (Box 24)
        Promotional record containing a radio ad for the third Velvet Underground album, read by New York DJ Bill “Rosko” Mercer and containing excerpts of “I'm Set Free,” “What Goes On,” and “Beginning To See The Light.”
      - The Velvet Underground. “Head Held High” b/w “Train Round the Bend.” France: Cotillion, Cat. no. 650 216 L., 1972; SR-9754 (Box 24)
        B-side title on sleeve reads: “Train Round the Bond.”
      - Appaloosa. “Rosie (Can You Feel It?)” b/w “Saved by Rock & Roll.” Baltimore: Concord Records, Cat. no. CR-003., 1973; SR-9755 (Box 24)
      - The Velvet Underground. “Sweet Jane” b/w “Rock & Roll.” Germany: Atlantic, Cat. no. ATL 10 339., 1973; SR-9756 (Box 24)
        “Trade sample” with hole punched through label.
      - Tina Harvey. “I’m Waiting for the Man” b/w “Baby, Let Me Follow You Down.” England: UK Records, Cat. no. UK 141., 1973; SR-9757 (Box 24)
      - The Velvet Underground. White Heat. [N.p.: No Label,] Cat. no. AEB 100., 1976; SR-9758 (Box 24)
        Bootleg EP
      - Lou Reed. Primitive: Pre-Velvets. [N.p.: No label], 1976; SR-9759 (Box 24)
        Contains 4 of Lou Reed’s pre-VU recordings with the Primitives, the Beachnuts, and the Roughnecks.
      - Third Rail. “Rondy Rush” b/w “Sweet Jane.” Boston: Rat Records, Cat. no. RR-5283., 1976; SR-9760 (Box 24)
      - Bryan Ferry. “What Goes On” b/w “Casanova.” [England]: Polydor/EG, Cat. no. POSP 3., 1978; SR-9761 (Box 24)
      - Nico. Four songs recorded live at CBGB, March 8, 1979. What Goes On Records., 1980; SR-9762 (Box 24)
        “What Goes On Records No. 1.”
      - Hellzephrys (Hellzephyrs Poporkester). “Varför Sitter Gamla Käringar Med Hatten På?” b/w “Ta en Kopp På Frelins!” Stockholm: R&P Records, Cat. no. RPS-3., 1982; SR-9763 (Box 24)
      - Coco M. “Walk on the Wildside (C’est la Ouate Version)” b/w “A Late Night.” Belgium: Dureco Benelux, Cat. no. 5269., 1987; SR-9764 (Box 24)
      - The Velvet Underground. “Foggy Notion” b/w “I Can’t Stand It.” Coxsackie, New York: Sundazed, Cat. no. S 227., 2011; SR-9765 (Box 24)
        Special “Record Store Day” 7” single of demos recorded at the Record Plant between May and October 1969.
      - The Velvet Underground. “After Hours.” New York: Manufactured by United Record Pressing for Johan Kugelberg/Rizzoli Books., 2009; SR-9766 (Box 24)
        Test pressing of the acetate demo of “After Hours”; this version of the pressing was rejected by Lou Reed.
      - The Velvet Underground. “After Hours.” New York: Manufactured by United Record Pressing for Johan Kugelberg/Rizzoli Books., 2009; SR-9767 (Box 24)
        Test pressing of the acetate demo of “After Hours”; this version of the pressing was accepted by Lou Reed. With ms. note and signature of Johan Kugelberg: “My copy.”
      - The Velvet Underground. “We’re Gonna Have a Real Good Time Together” b/w “If You Close the Door (After Hours).” Santa Monica, CA: Rizzoli International Publications/ Universal Music Special Markets, Cat. no. RÖV-0203-7., 2009; SR-9768 (Box 24)
        Unreleased acetates, issued in an edition of 100 and given away at events promoting The Velvet Underground: A New York Art. In silkscreen sleeve
    - Acetate discs, 1966-1969
      - The Velvet Underground. “Let’s Have a Real Good Time Together.” N.p., 1966-1969; SR-9769 (Box 22)
        33 1/3 RPM, Mono, 8”. Demo recording.
      - The Velvet Underground. “If You Close the Door (After Hours)”. [N.p.]: MGM/Verve Records, 1968; SR-9770 (Box 22)
      - The Velvet Underground. “If You Close the Door (After Hours)”. Hollywood, CA: DCT Recorders, 1968; SR-9771 (Box 22)
      - The Velvet Underground. “Jesus.” Hollywood, CA: DCT Recorders, 1968; SR-9772 (Box 24)
      - The Velvet Underground. “One Of These Days.” [N.p.], 1968-1969; SR-9773 (Box 22)
        10”. Demo recording
      - The Velvet Underground. “One Of These Days.” [N.p.], 1968-1969; SR-9774 (Box 22)
        10”. Alternative demo recording. In "Black Man's Cry" Sleeve.
  - Digital Audio Tapes (DAT), Undated
    - The Velvet Underground. “Velvet Underground 1969.”, Undated; TR-10888 (Box 24)
    - The Velvet Underground. “Doug Yule acetates.”, Undated; TR-10889 (Box 24)
  - CDs, 1988-2009
    - Officially-released CD boxed sets, 1993-2001
      - The Velvet Underground. "Bootleg Series Volume 1: The Quine Tapes."Universal Records, 2001; CD-2672-2675 (Box 25)
      - The Velvet Underground. "Final V.U. 1971-1973." Captain Trip Records, 2001 (4 Discs)., 2001; CD-2675-2678 (Box 27)
      - The Velvet Underground. "Peel Slowly and See." PolyGram Records, 1995; CD-2679-2683 (Box 27)
      - The Velvet Underground. "What Goes On." Raven Records, 1993; CD-2669-2671 (Box 27)
    - Officially-released CDs, 1988-2009
      - The Velvet Underground. "The Velvet Underground Live 1969 - Volume 1." PolyGram Records, 1988; CD-2685 (Box 25)
      - The Velvet Underground. "The Velvet Underground Live 1969 - Volume 2." PolyGram Records, 1988; CD-2686 (Box 25)
      - The Velvet Underground. "Loaded." Atlantic Recording Corp., 1997; CD-2687-2688 (Box 24)
      - The Velvet Underground. "The Velvet Underground and Nico." Deluxe Edition. Universal Records, 2002; CD-2689-2690 (Box 25)
      - The Velvet Underground. "The Velvet Underground Live at Max's Kansas City." Atlantic Records, 2004; CD-2691-2692 (Box 25)
      - Doug Yule. RedDog. "Hard Times", 2009; CD-2693 (Box 25)
    - Bootleg/Unofficially-released CDs, 1989-2007